{
    "toystory": [
        { "id": "1",
            "question": "From the following list who became Andy's toy first?",
            "choice1": "Jesse",
            "choice2": "Buzz",
            "choice3": "Bullseye",
            "hint": "To infinity and beyond.",
            "answer": "2"
        },
        { "id": "2",
            "question": "Who did Andy give the toys to when he went to college?",
            "choice1": "Bonnie",
            "choice2": "Molly",
            "choice3": "Gigs",
            "hint": "She created forky.",
            "answer": "1"
        },
        { "id": "3",
            "question": "What are Bo's sheep names?",
            "choice1": "Bobby, Gus and Lefty",
            "choice2": "Billy, Goat and Gruff",
            "choice3": "Amy, Lucy and Jan",
            "hint": "Title of a fairy tale.",
            "answer": "2"
        },
        { "id": "4",
            "question": "What was the first gift Andy opened at his Birthday Party?",
            "choice1": "Ms. Potato Head",
            "choice2": "Lunch box",
            "choice3": "Bed sheets",
            "hint": "It's time to eat.",
            "answer": "2"
        },
        { "id": "5",
            "question": "What was the name of the daycare the toys had to escape from?",
            "choice1": "Sunnyside Daycare",
            "choice2": "Moonside Daycare",
            "choice3": "Sunshine for Tots Daycare",
            "hint": "Lean on the side of sun.",
            "answer": "1"
        }
    ],
    "monsters": [
        { "id": "1",
          "question": "Who has blue fir and purple spots?",
          "choice1": "Boo",
          "choice2": "Mike",
          "choice3": "Sulley",
          "hint": "He has horns and two eyes.",
          "answer": "3"
        },
        { "id": "2",
            "question": "Who could become invisible?",
            "choice1": "Boo",
            "choice2": "Randall",
            "choice3": "Roz",
            "hint": "He 'Ran' around the room.",
            "answer": "2"
        },
        { "id": "3",
        "question": "What fraternity was Mike a part of?",
        "choice1": "OK (Oozma Kappa)",
        "choice2": "RΩR (Roar Omega Roar)",
        "choice3": "ΩH (Omega Howl)",
        "hint": "It all turned out 'ok'.",
        "answer": "1"
        },
        { "id": "4",
            "question": "What was the Librarian's name in Monsters University?",
            "choice1": "Claire Wheeler",
            "choice2": "Roz",
            "choice3": "Margaret Gesner",
            "hint": "Take a good 'ges' (sounds like: guess).",
            "answer": "3"
        },
        { "id": "5",
            "question": "What color was Boo's door?",
            "choice1": "Purple with yellow flowers.",
            "choice2": "White with purple and pink flowers.",
            "choice3": "Yellow",
            "hint": "Pink and purple are her favorite colors.",
            "answer": "2"
        }
    ],
    "grinch": [
        { "id": "1",
            "question": "What song was playing when the Grinch woke up at beginning of movie?",
            "choice1": "Santa Clause is coming to town",
            "choice2": "Feliz Navidad",
            "choice3": "12 days of Christmad",
            "hint": "Santa is key.",
            "answer": "1"
        },
        { "id": "2",
            "question": "What spray did the Grinch use to freshen up in the morning?",
            "choice1": "Slime Spray",
            "choice2": "Green Spruce",
            "choice3": "Mold Spice",
            "hint": "The spice of life.",
            "answer": "3"
        },
        { "id": "3",
        "question": "Who invited the Grinch to celebrate Christmas with the Who's?",
        "choice1": "Sue",
        "choice2": "Cindy Loo",
        "choice3": "Ida",
        "hint": "The girl with yellow hair and ponytails.",
        "answer": "2"
        },
        { "id": "4",
            "question": "How much did Grinch's heart grow?",
            "choice1": "3 sizes",
            "choice2": "2 sizes",
            "choice3": "4 sizes",
            "hint": "Three is the lucky number.",
            "answer": "1"
        },
        { "id": "5",
            "question": "What is Grinch's dog name?",
            "choice1": "Max",
            "choice2": "Rover",
            "choice3": "Spot",
            "hint": "MMMmmm.",
            "answer": "1"
        }
    ],
    "frozen": [
        { "id": "1",
          "question": "Where did Anna meet Kristoff?",
          "choice1": "In Summer Post",
          "choice2": "Ice Castle Trading",
          "choice3": "Wandering Oaken's Trading Post",
          "hint": "Don't wander too much.",
          "answer": "3"
        },
        { "id": "2",
            "question": "How did Anna become unfrozen at the end of Frozen?",
            "choice1": "An act of true love",
            "choice2": "Elsa was able to unfreeze her",
            "choice3": "True love kiss",
            "hint": "A sisters love.",
            "answer": "1"
        },
        { "id": "3",
            "question": "Who did Elsa create for Anna when they were younger?",
            "choice1": "Sven",
            "choice2": "Olaf",
            "choice3": "Snowgies",
            "hint": "Carrot nose.",
            "answer": "2"
        },
        { "id": "4",
            "question": "Who did Anna want to marry in Frozen?",
            "choice1": "Sven",
            "choice2": "Kristoff",
            "choice3": "Hans",
            "hint": "A prince from Southern Isles.",
            "answer": "3"
        },
        { "id": "5",
            "question": "Who is the older sister?",
            "choice1": "Anna",
            "choice2": "Elsa",
            "choice3": "their twins",
            "hint": "Who 'else' would it be.",
            "answer": "2"
        }
    ]
}